Brayden Murphy

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A detail oriented customer service representative with over seven years experience creating superb customer and client experiences with a variety of organizations ranging from food, retail, non-profit in home care and telecommunications. A team player that approaches technical challenges with tenacity and a people first attitude.

ACHIEVEMENT

- National Scholastic Aptitude Testing (SAT and ACT), 97th Percentile
- WUE Scholarship Winner, May 2011
- Western Washington University Honors Program
- Law School Admissions Test, 90th Percentile

CONTACT

PHONE:

208-514-9708

EMAIL:

murphy.brayden@gmail.com

1513 N. Tadpole Ct. Eagle, Idaho 83616

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Psychology

Western Washington University, Bellingham, WA, August 2015

High School Diploma, Advanced Course Work

Eagle High School, Eagle, ID, June 2011

WORK EXPERIENCE

T-Mobile - Customer Care Representative

December 2017 - Present

- Resolving customer concerns
- Technical troubleshooting
- Maintaining account documentation

Zen Bento - Kitchen Staff

April 2017 - November 2017

- Preparing food and monitoring for quality
- Ensuring food safety and workplace sanitation
- Submitting supply orders to keep kitchen well stocked

Target - Logistics Team Member

September 2016 - April 2017

- Providing friendly and prompt customer service
- Updating store records using a variety of applications
- Maintaining high standards for product presentation

DirecTV - Customer Service Representative

December 2015 - May 2016

- Resolving customer concerns
- Maintaining account documentation
- Providing tailored product offerings to customers

Evergreen Supported Living – Client Coordinator

August 2013 - June 2014

- Creating Positive Behavior and Individualized Instruction Plans
- Communicating client status and needs to guardians, program coordinator
- Reporting monthly summary of care and health to Board of Directors

Evergreen Supported Living - Living Skills Specialist

June 2013 - August 2015

- Providing quality care to developmentally disabled clients
- Facilitating community integration for clients
- Completing daily documentation of care